MARKO BERGER

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Ljudevita Jonkea, 3, 3 Zagreb, 10000 Croatia

PHONE

+38598209500

EMAIL

marko.berger@gmail.com

PLACE OF BIRTH

Zagreb

LINKS

Github

dev.to

LinkedIn

SKILLS

MySQL

• • • 0 0

CSS3

• • • 0 0

Angular

• • • • •

TypeScript

• • • •

Git

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

JavaScript

• • • 0 0

HTML5

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

Node,js

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

Vue.js

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

C# .NET

.

Golang

• • 0 0 0

PROFILE

I am a senior Angular Front-end developer with 5.5 years of experience in software development. I started using computers in 1987. When I wrote my first "Hello World!" computer program on Commodore 64 BASIC. Since then I was always into computer technology as it evolved. Now my technology stack is based on JavaScript / TypeScript programming languages and Angular framework. Also in my professional career, I have worked with Nx.monorepo, Ionic, .NET Core, C#, Node.js, Express.js NestJs and GO. I love brainstorming and working in creative teams. If I would describe myself, I would say "I'm a project-driven team player developer".

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Frontend developer, Asseco-See Croatia

Zagreb

Jan 2020

I was hired to be a Team lead and angular architect for developing a new fronted version of Asseco Live software with Angular framework. I was leading an international team (team members from Croatia, Ukraine, Belarus, and Russia).

My tasks were

- · architect design of the app
- \cdot on boarding new members
- · interviewing potential new developers for the entire Asseco-See Croatia
- · checking PR-s
- · giving tasks to team members
- writing documentation
- developing new features
- · writing tests in Jasmine and Jest

Tech stack

Angular 12, Angular Material, Sass, Nx monorepo, Jasmine, Karma, Jest, NGRX , Socket.IO

Fullstack developer, Intelegens j.d.o.o.

Zagreb

Apr 2018 — Jan 2020

Work as full stack developer on 3 projects.

- 1. Siemens proof of concept application Camera to OPC server
 - · Angular 4, CSS, Bootstrap 4, OPC lib, .Net-Core, C#
- 2. Peekator mobile app and angular app
 - · Ionic 4, Angular 5+, Sass, Angular Material, Node.js, Express.js, MySQL
- 3. Esspeta Performa 360 exam platform.
 - · Angular 6+, Sass, Angular Material, .Net Core, C#, MSSql

CEO, Gorice G.B. d.o.o.

Zagreb

Dec 2002 — Sep 2016

LANGUAGES

Croatian

.

English

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

I was appointed as CEO of the family furniture and interior firm and run it for 14 years.

I was in charge of:

- · key account management
- sales
- · project documentation
- employment
- logistics
- · client negotiations
- · supplier negotiations
- supervision
- · quality control

Key accounts: Konzum d.d., Tisak d.d., Stanić d.o.o., SDMS d.o.o., CRODUX d.o.o., Sony International, Mazda Jurković d.o.o.

Web Developer, Hearthstoneonline.com

Zagreb

Mar 2006 — Sep 2006

I was a freelancer for Hearthstoneonline.com from Barbados. There business was selling domains over the internet.

· PHP, MySql, HTML, CSS

EDUCATION

Highschool, Gimnazija Tituša Brezovačkog

Zagreb

Sep 2015 — Jun 1999

I graduated with the subject of Croatian, English, Physics and my final paper was on Linux.

Electronics, Tehničko Veleučilište Zagreb

Zagreb

Sep 1999 — Jun 2000

FOI Varaždin

Oct 2000 — Jan 2002

Networking, Splitsko Veleučilište

Zagreb

Oct 2002 — Oct 2006

Networking, VSITE

Zagreb

Oct 2011

Final dissertation left to do.

INTERNSHIPS

Frontend developer, Nivas d.o.o.

Zagreb

Oct 2017 — Nov 2017

Worked on Project management Angular project

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

President of Croatian Jewish youth , Jewish community of Zagreb

Zagreb

Dec 2001 — Sep 2010

I was appointed as president of Jewish youth in 2001. Where I represent Croatia in numerous leadership seminars and congresses. Like OSCE Congress on Antisemitism in Berlin 2004. WUJS congress in Haifa 2001 and more .